<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--

    Copyright (C) 2000 - 2011 Silverpeas

    This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
    it under the terms of the GNU Affero General Public License as
    published by the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the
    License, or (at your option) any later version.

    As a special exception to the terms and conditions of version 3.0 of
    the GPL, you may redistribute this Program in connection with Free/Libre
    Open Source Software ("FLOSS") applications as described in Silverpeas's
    FLOSS exception.  You should have recieved a copy of the text describing
    the FLOSS exception, and it is also available here:
    "http://www.silverpeas.com/legal/licensing"

    This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
    but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
    MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
    GNU Affero General Public License for more details.

    You should have received a copy of the GNU Affero General Public License
    along with this program.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.

-->
<WAComponent xmlns="http://silverpeas.org/xml/ns/component"
             xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
             xsi:schemaLocation="http://silverpeas.org/xml/ns/component http://www.silverpeas.org/xsd/component.xsd">
  <name>suggestionBox</name>
  <label>
    <message lang="fr">Boite à idées</message>
    <message lang="en">Suggestion Box</message>
    <message lang="de">Kummerkasten</message>
  </label>
  <description>
    <message lang="fr">La collaboration commence par l'obtention des avis des parties
      prenantes d'un projet. L'application boite à idées permet justement à chacun de participer en
      y proposant ses idées, de commenter les avis des autres et de voter ceux-ci
    </message>
    <message lang="en">Collaboration begins by obtaining the opinions of the stakeholders of a
      project.
      The suggestion box allows for everyone to participate by offering their ideas, by commenting
      on
      other reviews and by voting them
    </message>
    <message lang="de">Die Zusammenarbeit beginnt mit Erhalt der Stellungnahmen der Beteiligten
      eines
      Projekts. Der Kummerkasten ermöglicht für jedermann zu, indem sie ihre Ideen zu beteiligen,
      durch Kommentare zu anderen Bewertungen und ihnen durch Abstimmung
    </message>
  </description>
  <suite>
    <message lang="fr">02 Gestion Collaborative</message>
    <message lang="en">02 Collaborative Management</message>
    <message lang="de">02 kollaborative Verwaltung</message>
  </suite>
  <visible>true</visible>
  <portlet>false</portlet>
  <instanceClassName>org.silverpeas.components.suggestionbox.SuggestionBoxInstanciator
  </instanceClassName>
  <profiles>
    <profile name="admin">
      <label>
        <message lang="fr">Gestionnaires</message>
        <message lang="en">Administrators</message>
        <message lang="de">Administrator</message>
      </label>
      <help>
        <message lang="fr">Les gestionnaires paramètrent la boite à idées. Ils y précisent, via
          l'édito, l'objectif de la boite à idées et quelles sont les règles en vigueur dans la
          participation.
        </message>
        <message lang="en">The administrators parameterize the suggestion box idea. They specify,
          via
          the edito, the purpose of the suggestion box and what are the rules of participation.
        </message>
        <message lang="de">Die Administratoren Parametrieren Sie den Kummerkasten. Geben Sie über
          die Redak, der Zweck der Kummerkasten und was sind die Regeln für die Beteiligung.
        </message>
      </help>
    </profile>
    <profile name="publisher">
      <label>
        <message lang="fr">Publieurs</message>
        <message lang="en">Publishers</message>
        <message lang="de">Herausgeber</message>
      </label>
      <help>
        <message lang="fr">Les publieurs ont pour rôle de valider les idées des participants.
          Lorsqu'une idée est validée, celle-ci est alors publiée dans la boite à idées. Toute idée,
          qu'elle soit validée ou refusée, est annotée par le publieur. La note d'une idée validée
          donne
          des informations supplémentaires, et la note d'une idée refusée informe au participant
          les raisons du refus. Le publieur peut modérer l'idée avant sa publication.
        </message>
        <message lang="en">The role of the publieurs is to validate the suggestions of the
          participants.
          When an idea is validated, it is then published in the suggestion box. Any suggestion,
          validated or rejected, is endorsed by the publisher. The note on a validated suggestion
          provides additional information whereas the note on a rejected suggestion informs
          the participant the reasons of the refusal. The publisher can moderate the suggestion
          before its publication.
        </message>
        <message lang="de">Die Rolle der publieurs ist es, die Anregungen der Teilnehmer zu
          überprüfen.
          Wenn eine Idee bestätigt ist, wird es dann in der Kummerkasten veröffentlicht. Alle
          Anregungen
          werden von einem Verlag mit einem Hinweis bestätigt oder abgelehnt werden. Der Anmerkung
          auf eine validierte Vorschlag enthält zusätzliche Informationen, während die Notiz auf
          Vorschlag einem abgelehnt informierte die Teilnehmer Gründe für die Ablehnung. Der Verlag
          kann die Idee, vor der Veröffentlichung moderieren.
        </message>
      </help>
    </profile>
    <profile name="writer">
      <label>
        <message lang="fr">Rédacteurs</message>
        <message lang="en">Writers</message>
        <message lang="de">Redaktor</message>
      </label>
      <help>
        <message lang="fr">Les rédacteurs sont les participants d'une boite à idées. Ils proposent
          des
          idées, commentent et votent celles des autres.
        </message>
        <message lang="en">The writers are the participants in a suggestion box. They propose
          suggestions,
          they vote and comment on those of others.
        </message>
        <message lang="de">Die Redaktor sind die Teilnehmer in einem Kummerkasten. Sie schlagen vor
          Anregungen, sie bewerten und kommentieren die der anderen.
        </message>
      </help>
    </profile>
    <profile name="user">
      <label>
        <message lang="fr">Lecteurs</message>
        <message lang="en">Readers</message>
        <message lang="de">Leser</message>
      </label>
      <help>
        <message lang="fr">Les lecteurs ne participent pas à une boite à idées. Ils ne peuvent que
          consulter les idées proposées et les échanges.
        </message>
        <message lang="en">Readers don't participate in a suggestion box. They can only view the
          proposed suggestions and exchanges.
        </message>
        <message lang="de">Leser nicht in einem Kummerkasten beteiligen. Sie können nur die
          vorgeschlagenen Anregungen und Austausch zu sehen.
        </message>
      </help>
    </profile>
  </profiles>
</WAComponent>